<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fitness Week</string>
    <string name="slide1_description">Is a personal trainer which will provide your with a series of tools and information that will help you achieve all your goals.</string>
    <string name="slide2_description">More than 300 exercises with wich you can perform very varied routines in the gym,in home or street. Each exercise has its respective explanation,illustrative images and an explanatory video,so that you can execute correctly each exercise.</string>
    <string name="slide3_description">Different routines that will help you plan your weekly work, you will findn routines of 3,4,5 or 6 days a week taking into account whether you are beginner, intermediate or advanced, including 3,4 and 5 day routines designed specially for women.</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="skip">skip</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_main">NavigationMainActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="tips_subtitle">How to accelerate your metabolism to lose weight fast</string>
    <string name="sample_text1">lthe metabolse bbolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlreibolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei bolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlreiolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei bolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeoglthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog flwfjwe pof weojffew wefjiowef jwefwejf weifewoiefew fowefjioweif oiwesfjiowee  jeof jefeijf seiegrog reoigjroig srgriog rego grg gjrsoigujer</string>
    <string name="toolbar_title">Tips</string>
    <string name="demotext">lfsfjlk f f fkf lfjslf dksdjf sdfj sdlkfjds fjf lkekfjel felkfj elkfjerklf erklflefje lfjedklf edljeklf ekf jeiof jerf erierjfkler jfkler jflkefjerklfjlkerfjerlkkkerjg lkeregjlgerejklerjglker jklerjgekllg ggggjelk glkdjglkergjdrlgjlkg jkf asjfkljfklew ajflkewef;jew\'fje ej ea fl fjkleefjwalf;jwelekf wfla ej fej fje wfwejef efj jf efj e; fwejfjwekflw fjwelkfjewafweke fewlkfj jfw ejfejfawew fewj fc jeawef jwe f jwea jf jwe jge jwgt j jwj g j j wg jolgjeslkfjewrk</string>
    <string name="box_string_a">Stand beside object to be cleared. Bring knees up and jump vertically but also laterally off ground and over the barrier. Land on both feet and immediately jump the other direction over barrier.</string>
    <string name="box_string_b">Stand facing box with feet slightly wider than hip-width apart. Lower body into a semi-squat position and immediately jump up onto box. Do not hold a squat position before jumping up keep the time between dipping down and jumping up to a minimum.</string>
    <string name="box_string_c">Stand side on to box with feet slightly wider than hip-width apart. Lower body into a semi-squat position and jump up onto box. Do not hold a squat position before jumping up keep the time between dipping down and jumping up to a minimum. Feet should land softly on box. Step back down (not jump back down) and repeat.</string>
    <string name="box_string_d">Stand on box with toes close to edge, feet shoulder width apart. Step off (do not jump off) box and land on both feet. Immediately jump up as high as possible and reach up with both hands towards. The jump should be vertical with no horizontal movement. Ground contact time should be short unlike in the diagram. Landing should be soft.</string>
    <string name="box_string_e">Stand to side of box and place the left foot on top of box. Push off the box using the left leg only and explode vertically as high as possible. Drive the arms forward and up for maximum height. Land with right foot on the box and left foot on the ground to the other side of the box.</string>
    <string name="whey_protein">Whey protein or meat protein, which is better ?</string>
    <string name="the_4_supplements">The 4 supplements that you shoudl consume if you have low budget</string>
    <string name="how_to_recognize">How to recognize a good supplement to optimize your profits</string>
    <string name="do_not">Do not start a diet that will endosome day start a lifestyle that lasts forever</string>
    <string name="take_some">Take some time to take care of your diet</string>
    <string name="go_to_market">Go to market and buy fresh product</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up to the method</string>
    <string name="balanced_diet">Balanced diet and exercise, the perfect</string>
    <string name="do_you_like">Do you like to cook? Why not sign up for a cooking course in order to get more out of your food ? In this way, in addition to being able to meet people with the cooking, new technologies, new rich, simple and undoubtedly healthy option.</string>
    <string name="in_a_calm">In a calm and relaxed atmosphere. Being aware of what you are going to eat and spending some time will help you possible compulsive and emotional intake. It will help you improve your ability to control with food.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout1_description">The metabolism is defined as a physical-chemical process that takes place in the body and whose function is to process (to use a simple term) the ingested food to take advantage of its energies and nutrients. Virtually the metabolism is responsible for regulating our daily functions so that their role is essential to maintain a balanced life. The higher the metabolic rate, the greater the energy consumption and nutrient assimilation, and therefore, the greater and better results in all aspects of life: intellectual, physical, emotional, etc. At the same time, talking about metabolism comes with the package talking about fat combustion, and the process that takes advantage of the energies found in food. A person with a better metabolic rate can use higher fat reserves, since it requires more energy to maintain their vital functions, from the most basic (such as thinking or breathing) to the most complex (digest food, repair damaged tissues, etc.) . Hence the reason why talking about metabolism is so important when we start our sporting life, because in summary, an improvement in this will help us obtain more optimal results. 1. Increase muscle volume Increase muscle volume is the first step to take into account when seeking to improve the ratio of metabolic rate. This is where the workouts with loads develop a fundamental role, since it is through the heavy work that the muscles can develop, as part of a defense mechanism to survive in a hostile environment. By having a greater muscle mass the basal metabolism increases and therefore the caloric intake of the body becomes greater, allowing the combustion of fat, even when at rest is much more effective compared to an average person. 2. Improve your diet Someone who trains with a lot of effort but who leads a poor and careless dietary regime, very few chances of success will have, because it is through the nutrients that the body can perform its internal functions in an adequate way to show optimal external results. To give an example we can take the case of an athlete who seeks to eliminate excess body fat. Oddly enough, the most recommended strategy to follow is to eat a diet high in healthy fats and proteins, which will allow the body to enter a state of ketosis where accumulated fat will act as the main source of energy. 3. Train with greater intensity When we talk about burning fats, cardio is considered as the alternative par excellence, being that in fact there are many more effective methods to get rid of the accumulated caloric surplus in the body. In this case, the option that is positioned above all is HIIT, or High Intensity Interval Training, by its acronym in English, with which it is possible to burn more calories in a 15-minute session than in a cardio workout Regular for 40 minutes. But beware, that this premise does not refer to the fact that with HIIT there is a huge caloric consumption in neither time, but this is where the fact that they import more burnt calories throughout the day than those burned during the training. When carrying out a session of HIIT, an effect known as COPD is triggered in the body and it refers to the Pöst-Training Oxygen Consumption (for its acronym in English) and that it is a process that leads the body to have a greater consumption energy by requiring more oxygen during the hours following exercise. In this way, HIIT and consequently, COPD, can be interpreted as the definitive way to burn fat while watching television. Of course, it must be taken into account that HIIT is a very intense training method and therefore, under no circumstances is it recommended to be carried out by people suffering from heart problems, being overweight or having a low physical condition. Conclusions As you can already imagine, having a healthy body costs, and not only economically, but also physically and mentally. When it comes to losing fat there are many factors that must be taken into account to achieve total success progressively and thus not stagnate to throw in the towel when you are already halfway. In spite of how complicated it can be at first, in the long run, you will see that knowing all the secrets (which should not be secret) for effective fat burning, will not represent even the slightest obstacle to achieve your goal</string>
    <string name="tips_layout2_description">We know that in the world of fitness we can come up against a long list of obstacles that in one way or another stand in our way, even after many years of experience. But come on, nobody said that the process of body transformation would be easy. And one of these difficulties, which lurks both beginners and advanced athletes, refers to the moment you have to choose a supplement that helps us optimize our muscle mass gains, especially when it comes to protein that, undoubtedly, is one of the supplements Must have in the repertoire of every amateur and professional bodybuilder. And you do not need to go deep into the subject to understand that protein is one of the main allies when it comes to gaining muscle mass. Increase in the recovery, better performance, reach the adequate nutritional requirements, among others, are the main factors by which the protein powder takes vital importance in the life of any passionate to crush the iron, as some would say. But, why is there so much doubt or controversy regarding protein supplements? From the outset, we know that as the years have passed, the scientific research to find the holy grail of muscle building, have advanced by leaps and bounds. Todays bodybuilders are fortunate to have a database a thousand times larger than pure information, compared to bodybuilders who trained during the era of greats like Arnold Schwarzenegger, to mention some example. Unfortunately, the excess of information, although it is appreciated, can not always be used by everyone to the fullest. There are times when handling so much data can be so stressful and frustrating that it ends up causing confusion and, of course, disinformation. A clear example of this? The excess of supplements that, although they have proved to be effective, do not pose more than a nuisance for many of the bodybuilders when they bump into the counter of the sports store to choose the ideal product and see that they have dozens and dozens of supplements to choose from that just does not seem to make sense. At the end of the day what many end up doing (especially the least prepared) is to buy several supplements of different names but with the same function, assuming a huge expenditure of money and without the possibility of achieving better results, by not having additional external help that really worth it. Whey protein and meat protein are two products that are always in the eye of bodybuilders. Although the first of them has more time in the market, the second is also often well consulted because many believe that coming from a source of protein such as meat, may end up offering more benefits compared to its counterpart. But what is true about all this? Is meat protein actually better than whey protein? or, is it the other way around? Then we will examine both later to be able to draw our own conclusions In conclusion After analyzing each of the points mentioned above, we can arrive at the simple conclusion that beef protein is much better in all aspects, buying them with those of whey protein. The popularity of this last product may be due to the fact that it has become a pioneer in the world of bodybuilding, accompanying throughout its career the bodybuilders of the golden age who undoubtedly achieved important changes without the advantages we have today. day. If you have never consumed beef protein, you still have the opportunity to do so and try the benefits it offers. Yes, perhaps for many it can be tedious because it offers a less pleasant taste compared to its competitor, however, this is a small price that is worth paying when it comes to optimizing muscle mass gains.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout3_description">Whether professionally or amatéur, the consumption of supplements is very common in the world of fitness. And is that for decades, the industry has made us believe that to reach the limit of the body in terms of muscle mass growth is concerned, it is necessary to resort to the consumption of these substances. The fact of including this type of products in the diet is already at the discretion of each and if your case is that of an athlete who is starting with their training and want to consume supplements to improve, go ahead, you can always have many options , even if you have a very tight budget. For that reason we have decided to create this little guide that will help you to know the most important supplements on your way to the final transformation of your body. 1. Creatine It does not matter who you ask, but it is very likely that more than 90% of those who know the subject will tell you that the most important supplement for a good development of muscle mass is creatine. Yes, unlike what many believe, Whey protein does not provide as much benefit in relation to cost if we compare it with creatine, which in addition to its low price, is effective for: • Improve physical performance when training • Speed up the muscle recovery process • Increase bone mineral density • Accelerate glucose consumption (increased metabolism) • Reduce oxidative stress due to free radicals that occur with high intensity workouts • Maximize mental performance Many studies claim that to achieve all these effects of creatine is necessary to consume up to 0.25 grams per kilogram of weight, which in summary refers to a person weighing 70 kilos must consume approximately 17.5 grams of creatine a day. If we take into account that the chicken breast provides only 3.4 grams of creatine per kilogram, reaching the recommended figure is extremely difficult, if not impossible, even if we are willing to consume exuberant amounts of food in our day to day. 2. Protein Whether it is whey protein, soy protein, meat protein, etc., it is a highly recommended type of product for anyone who is starting out in the world of muscle building. Unlike creatine, the protein provides all the amino acids that the body requires to perform all its functions, including giving way to muscle growth. However, the reason why the consumption of creatine over protein is recommended is because the latter does not provide the necessary amounts of amino acids to maximize the expected results. Come on, that the rest of essential amino acids can be obtained through the diet, while the amino acids necessary for the formation of creatine (L-arginine, Glycine and L-Methionine) are not so abundant, but simply sufficient for the average needs . The protein powder can be obtained in any supplement store or sports stores, even in some gyms it is completely normal to see some boats for sale. 3. Fish oil and multivitamins Multivitamins, although not essential, can make the difference between optimal performance and mediocre performance. It is true that most of the vitamins and minerals are obtained through food, however, due to the hectic current pace of life that many of us have today, it is difficult to prepare more elaborate meals with a high variety of fruits and vegetables. They are responsible for providing these nutrients. This is where multivitamins come into play, which are even necessary for many people who, in addition to not training, do not pay much attention to the foods they consume on a daily basis. 4. Pre-training If your budget allows it, you can even give higher priority to pre-workout supplements over multivitamins. This is because, as we mentioned before, vitamins and minerals can be easily obtained through the diet, while the benefits of a pre-workout supplement, we will hardly get them in this way. This is because supplements of this type are aimed at improving performance when performing routine exercises that may be overshadowed by the stress of everyday activities. In other words, a pre-training supplement not only helps to have a better performance, but also gives us that energy necessary to find the motivation that is often affected by the fatigue caused by the tasks of modern life.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout4_description">The world of sports supplements is so vast that literally, today we can find in the market hundreds of dozens of products that promise to optimize our profits, depending on the objective we have in mind. The number of options is so high that for someone who has never consumed any supplement can find tedious the fact of having to choose one without the fear of throwing your money because it does not suit your needs, or has been manufactured by a company that offers products of dubious origin and of which there is no favorable record as to the effectiveness of these. 1: Choose products from recognized brands You must bear in mind that in this case we are talking about supplements, that is, a product that will take you to the body and that will surely play a fundamental role in the way you get your results. Due to the importance of this, take into account the products of the most recognized brands as the first option, even if they are alternatives that have a higher cost, because at the end of the day they have the backing of a company with journey in the world of fitness and that surely more than one person will recommend you without thinking. 2: Beware of new arrivals Due to the large number of options we have available, not everyone risks making large investments in the supplement market, so be very careful with the new brands that appear overnight. Remember that manufacturing or synthesizing a supplement requires a thorough investigation that can last up to years, so as far as possible, try to avoid buying brand new products, unless you are sure that behind them there is a clinical certification or at least it has been scientifically proven to measure the effectiveness of what is offered. 3: It does not only matter who makes them, but also who sells them Remember that between making a supplement from scratch and finally selling it on the market, there is a big difference. Many do not know this and therefore, there are those who take advantage to sell the supplements in sporadic places or even exclusively in online stores to make a business only beneficial for them, leaving the consumer with the tail between the legs. And is that if you find very tempting offers such as discounts of 50 or 60%, but these are only available through the Internet, it is very likely that this is because what they are selling is not really a supplement or , it may be an expired product that must be removed from the inventory. Even, in the worst case, it may happen that what you are buying are actually hormones that work as anabolics, which are illegal substances in most countries. 4: Leave the product the benefit of the doubt Finally, if you see that the product is reliable enough to give it a chance, you can do so by purchasing the smallest or most affordable presentation you can find. Once you have the product in hand, keep training in the same way, feed yourself as usual and consume the supplement as indicated on the label. Do this for a month and take a detailed record of your measurements, sensations after having taken it, those that occur throughout the day and also those that you feel when you train. After having spent this time, if everything goes without a complication, summarize everything you wrote down and compare your results with those of the first day. Did you improve in the trainings? Have you gained muscle mass? Did you lose fat? If you have intolerable side effects during the test, it is best to suspend the use of the product, consult with the doctor to rule out any complications and make way for a new supplement if necessary. In conclusion Remember that while supplements are important for proper development, they are not always necessary. Surely in your gym they will try to sell you from the first days, but before making any investment, first make sure that your macronutrients are possible with the diet exclusively. If not, then go for a supplement, following the above points to choose the option that best suits your needs. Although the supplements are ideal to maximize the results, these will only be effective when the trainings are carried out in the best way and of course, a proper diet is followed, so do not think that just by taking some fitness product you will get remarkable results in a short time, well no; You should not consider it as miracle products."</string>
    <string name="tips_layout5_description">The active ingredient The world of supplementation goes beyond powdered proteins. The market has to offer supplements that act as fat burning enhancers or to solve nutritional imbalances, in order to improve the performance of the athlete, either at the time of training, or during daily activities of the day, as They can be, work. For that reason, it is important as a first point, to know how to choose the active ingredient. An athlete looking to gain muscle, should look for protein-based supplements, while another who is in the definition stage, could opt for an additional fat burner with Egcg or caffeine, which act as stimulants and accelerate metabolism. As already mentioned before, everything depends on the type of objective of each person. Reading the label The label speaks a lot about the supplement that is thought to be acquired, because it contains not only the concentration of the active ingredient, but also other compounds that can be stored in the product. Some labels can even mention the place from which the active ingredient has been extracted, although not referring to the geographical location, but rather to the part of the animal or vegetable. Absorption of the active ingredient While the absorption time of the active ingredient is important to take advantage of the properties it provides, it is very difficult to find the time described on the product label, since most companies omit this small detail in the presentations of the supplements . Manufacturers must submit their products to dissolution tests to ensure that they can be absorbed properly and thus ensure their effectiveness. Allergen compounds It is very important to know if the products to choose have or not with ingredients that can unleash a sensibility in the organism of the one who thinks to consume them. For example, a person who is allergic to dairy products should avoid the consumption of supplements made in machines that use milk for the manufacture of others, or that already include lactose in the product, such as whey protein. Another of the most frequent consternations about supplements is their possible content of gluten, a wheat protein that causes unfavorable reactions in people suffering from celiac disease. In these cases, it is best to opt for products that include the legend hypoallergenic on the label, or those that mention specifically not contain some common allergenic ingredients such as wheat, gluten, lactose, nuts, etc. Lifetime of the products The pieces of cotton that are included in the packaging of some vitamin supplements, or even drugs in the form of capsules or tablets are known as desiccants and their function is to act as a harmless for the absorption of moisture found inside of the container, to allow the pills to remain dry and in good condition for a longer time. However, the desiccant is only effective until the product is opened for the first time, so in doing this, the most recommended is to discard the cotton, since it will not be able to continue to absorb moisture any longer, so that all the accumulation It would fall on the pills, deteriorating its quality.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout6_description">Start a lifestyle that lasts forever. Look for a healthy and balanced diet and lifestyle according to your tastes, your habits, lifestyle and goals. In this way you will ensure that it is a lasting food over time.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout7_description">The pace of life that we currently have makes us not spend much time or pay attention to what we eat. What consequences do we have? Commit health, by consuming more frequently and frequently fast food or unhealthy foods. Sit down to plan your own eating plan. If you know what you have to eat, you will know what you have to buy and it will be easier for you to stick to it.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout8_description">Reserve one hour a week to get closer to the market to buy seasonal products. Put aside the calculation of the total calories you consume. Food not only feeds us but nourishes us. You must think of food as a set of nutrients that will help the body to function properly. So focus on choosing foods of good nutritional quality.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout9_description">I advise you to keep in mind the dish method that will help you ensure that they are balanced, several and to delimit quantities. Always give preference, with half of your plate, to both raw and cooked vegetables. With salads the amount ingested is not usually enough, so you should not forget to also consume vegetables. A quarter of a plate should be protein in the form of egg, meat, fish, seafood, vegetable protein or legume. The other quarter of the plate should be composed of carbohydrates such as pasta, rice, potato or bread. The dessert can be a piece of fruit or a dairy dessert.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout10_description">Mark it on the calendar, introduce it into your daily routine, so that the excuses of our day to day can not do it. The practice of physical exercise on a regular basis will help you improve your fitness and your health. In addition, it generates endorphins and brings well-being. Look for a sport that you like, that makes you enjoy and that you find it easy to introduce in your day to day.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout11_description">Food is still one of the greatest pleasures we have, so you can also enjoy eating healthy. If there are foods that you do not like, nothing happens. Focus on those foods that you can if you can eat, that you like, in this wide range of possibilities you have and not in that large minority that you should limit. Go ahead and try new foods, combinations that allow you not only to eat well, but to enjoy it.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout12_description">Can you take a perfect diet? Is life? Are we? Of course not, so we should not demand to do everything perfect. If so, you will not appreciate the small advances or improvements you make in your areas and the minimum, you will feel frustrated and unmotivated. It is not a perfect diet what you should get, but a healthy and balanced behavior and lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout13_description">Clean the pantry. The presence at home of healthy foods increases the chance of success. It could be said that it is a determining factor of short and long-term success. If you have nothing prepared and you have to improvise, having unhealthy foods in your pantry or refrigerator will make it difficult for you to eat well or eat what you had in mind.</string>


    <string name="how_to_accelerate">How to accelerate your metabolism to lose weight fast</string>
<string name="atras">Back</string>
<string name="b">Squats</string>
<string name="ba">Step Ups Jump</string>
<string name="baDesc">Place yourself in front of an exercise box, raise the left leg and then the right until it is full of it, then lower the right leg and equal the left, this will be a repetition</string>
    <string name="guide_to_choose_your_sepplement">Guide to choose your sepplement</string>
    <string name="enjoy_your_food">Enjoy your food</string>
    <string name="in_your">If your are on diet, do not go self-demanding</string>
    <string name="improve_your_enviroment">Improve your enviroment</string>
    <string name="eat_consciously">Eat consciously</string>
    <string name="he_chef">Get the chef you have inside</string>
    <string name="how_to_acclerate">How to accelerate your metabolism to lose weight fast</string>
    <string name="why_protein">Why protein or meat protein, which is better ?</string>
    <string name="get_the_chef">Get the chef you have inside</string>
    <string name="if_you_are">if your are on a diet, do not go self-demanding</string>

</resources>
