<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fitness Week</string>
    <string name="slide1_description">Is a personal trainer which will provide your with a series of tools and information that will help you achieve all your goals.</string>
    <string name="slide2_description">More than 300 exercises with wich you can perform very varied routines in the gym,in home or street. Each exercise has its respective explanation,illustrative images and an explanatory video,so that you can execute correctly each exercise.</string>
    <string name="slide3_description">Different routines that will help you plan your weekly work, you will findn routines of 3,4,5 or 6 days a week taking into account whether you are beginner, intermediate or advanced, including 3,4 and 5 day routines designed specially for women.</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="skip">skip</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_main">NavigationMainActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="tips_subtitle">How to accelerate your metabolism to lose weight fast</string>
    <string name="sample_text1">lthe metabolse bbolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlreibolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei bolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlreiolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei bolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeoglthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog lthe metabolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo eoe feopfeog gfej erjerlrei esgfes eojf feoi geog geo gjeog flwfjwe pof weojffew wefjiowef jwefwejf weifewoiefew fowefjioweif oiwesfjiowee  jeof jefeijf seiegrog reoigjroig srgriog rego grg gjrsoigujer</string>
    <string name="toolbar_title">Tips</string>
    <string name="demotext">lfsfjlk f f fkf lfjslf dksdjf sdfj sdlkfjds fjf lkekfjel felkfj elkfjerklf erklflefje lfjedklf edljeklf ekf jeiof jerf erierjfkler jfkler jflkefjerklfjlkerfjerlkkkerjg lkeregjlgerejklerjglker jklerjgekllg ggggjelk glkdjglkergjdrlgjlkg jkf asjfkljfklew ajflkewef;jew\'fje ej ea fl fjkleefjwalf;jwelekf wfla ej fej fje wfwejef efj jf efj e; fwejfjwekflw fjwelkfjewafweke fewlkfj jfw ejfejfawew fewj fc jeawef jwe f jwea jf jwe jge jwgt j jwj g j j wg jolgjeslkfjewrk</string>
    <string name="box_string_a">Stand beside object to be cleared. Bring knees up and jump vertically but also laterally off ground and over the barrier. Land on both feet and immediately jump the other direction over barrier.</string>
    <string name="box_string_b">Stand facing box with feet slightly wider than hip-width apart. Lower body into a semi-squat position and immediately jump up onto box. Do not hold a squat position before jumping up keep the time between dipping down and jumping up to a minimum.</string>
    <string name="box_string_c">Stand side on to box with feet slightly wider than hip-width apart. Lower body into a semi-squat position and jump up onto box. Do not hold a squat position before jumping up keep the time between dipping down and jumping up to a minimum. Feet should land softly on box. Step back down (not jump back down) and repeat.</string>
    <string name="box_string_d">Stand on box with toes close to edge, feet shoulder width apart. Step off (do not jump off) box and land on both feet. Immediately jump up as high as possible and reach up with both hands towards. The jump should be vertical with no horizontal movement. Ground contact time should be short unlike in the diagram. Landing should be soft.</string>
    <string name="box_string_e">Stand to side of box and place the left foot on top of box. Push off the box using the left leg only and explode vertically as high as possible. Drive the arms forward and up for maximum height. Land with right foot on the box and left foot on the ground to the other side of the box.</string>

</resources>
