<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fitness Week</string>
    <string name="slide1_description">Is a personal trainer which will provide your with a series of tools and information that will help you achieve all your goals.</string>
    <string name="slide2_description">More than 300 exercises with wich you can perform very varied routines in the gym,in home or street. Each exercise has its respective explanation,illustrative images and an explanatory video,so that you can execute correctly each exercise.</string>
    <string name="slide3_description">Different routines that will help you plan your weekly work, you will findn routines of 3,4,5 or 6 days a week taking into account whether you are beginner, intermediate or advanced, including 3,4 and 5 day routines designed specially for women.</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="skip">skip</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_main">NavigationMainActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="tips_subtitle">How to accelerate your metabolism to lose weight fast</string>
    <string name="sample_text1">lthe metabolse bbolse is defind as a phtsucka cgenuqaak eofe feoifeomi egfeoi geiuueo </string>
    <string name="toolbar_title">Tips</string>
    <string name="demotext">lfsfjlk f f fkf lfjslf dksdjf sdfj sdlkfjds fjf lkekfjel felkfj elkfjerklf erklflefje lfjedklf edljeklf ekf jeiof jerf erierjfkler jfkler jflkefjerklfjlkerfjerlkkkerjg lkeregjlgerejklerjglker jklerjgekllg ggggjelk glkdjglkergjdrlgjlkg jkf asjfkljfklew ajflkewef;jew\'fje ej ea fl fjkleefjwalf;jwelekf wfla ej fej fje wfwejef efj jf efj e; fwejfjwekflw fjwelkfjewafweke fewlkfj jfw ejfejfawew fewj fc jeawef jwe f jwea jf jwe jge jwgt j jwj g j j wg jolgjeslkfjewrk</string>
    <string name="box_string_a">Stand beside object to be cleared. Bring knees up and jump vertically but also laterally off ground and over the barrier. Land on both feet and immediately jump the other direction over barrier.</string>
    <string name="box_string_b">Stand facing box with feet slightly wider than hip-width apart. Lower body into a semi-squat position and immediately jump up onto box. Do not hold a squat position before jumping up keep the time between dipping down and jumping up to a minimum.</string>
    <string name="box_string_c">Stand side on to box with feet slightly wider than hip-width apart. Lower body into a semi-squat position and jump up onto box. Do not hold a squat position before jumping up keep the time between dipping down and jumping up to a minimum. Feet should land softly on box. Step back down (not jump back down) and repeat.</string>
    <string name="box_string_d">Stand on box with toes close to edge, feet shoulder width apart. Step off (do not jump off) box and land on both feet. Immediately jump up as high as possible and reach up with both hands towards. The jump should be vertical with no horizontal movement. Ground contact time should be short unlike in the diagram. Landing should be soft.</string>
    <string name="box_string_e">Stand to side of box and place the left foot on top of box. Push off the box using the left leg only and explode vertically as high as possible. Drive the arms forward and up for maximum height. Land with right foot on the box and left foot on the ground to the other side of the box.</string>


    <!-- Chest Exercise data-->
    <string name="PEC1">Bench Presses\n\nLie faceup on a horizontal bench, with buttocks on the bench and feet ﬂat on the ground: \n• Grasp the barbell with an overhand grip wider than shoulder width. \n• Inhale and lower the bar to the chest with a controlled movement. \n• Extend the arms and exhale at the end of the effort. \nThis exercise engages me complete pectoralis major muscle, pectoralis minor. anterior deltoid. serratus anterior, and coracobrachialis. \nVariations \n1. This movement may be perfomed while arching the back power-lifter style. This position brings the more powerful lower part of the pectoral muscle into play, allowing you to lift heavier weights. \n2. Executing the extension with the elbows next to the body concentrates the work onto the anterior deltoid. \n3. Varying the width of the hands isolates different parts of the muscle: \n • Hands closer together isolates the central part of the pectorals. \n • Hands wider apart isolates the lateral part of the pectorals. \n4. Varying the angle of the barbell isolates different parts of the muscle: \n• Lowering the bar to the chondrocostal border of the rib cage isolates the lower part of the pectorals. \n • Lowering the barbell onto the middle part of the pectorals isolates the midline ﬁbers. \n • Lowering the bar onto the sternal notch isolates the elavicular head of the muscle. \n5. If you have back problems or want to isolate the pectcrals, perform the extension with the legs raised. \n6. Perform the extension at a frame that guides the bar.</string>
    <string name="PEC10">Peck Deck Flyes\n\nSit at the machine with the arms open and horizontal, bent at the elbows. Rest the forearms on the pads. with the forearms and wrists relaxed: \n • Inhale and squeeze the arms together. Exhale at the end ot the movement. \nThis exercise works the pectoralis major by stretching it. As the elbows come together, focus the effort onto the sternal head of the pectoralis major. \nThis exercise also develops the coracobrachialis and the short head ot the biceps brachii. Long sets allow you to pump the muscles intensely. \nThis exercise helps beginners develop enough strength to move onto more complex movements.</string>
    <string name="PEC11">Incline Dumbbell Presses\n\nLie back on an incline bench with a dumbbell in each hand atop your thighs. The palms of your hands will be facing each other. \nThen, using your thighs to help push the dumbbells up, lift the dumbbells one at a time so that you can hold them at shoulder width. \nOnce you have the dumbbells raised to shoulder width, rotate your wrists forward so that the palms of your hands are facing away from you. This will be your starting position. \nBe sure to keep full control of the dumbbells at all times. Then breathe out and push the dumbbells up with your chest. \nLock your arms at the top, hold for a second, and then start slowly lowering the weight. Tip Ideally, lowering the weights should take about twice as long as raising them. \nRepeat the movement for the prescribed amount of repetitions. \nWhen you are done, place the dumbbells back on your thighs and then on the floor. This is the safest manner to release the dumbbells. \nVariations: You can use several angles on the incline bench if the bench you are using is adjustable. \nAnother variation of this exercise is to perform it with the palms of the hands facing each other. \nAlso, you can perform the exercise with the palms facing each other and then twisting the wrist as you lift the dumbbells so that at the top of the movement the palms are facing away from the body. I personally do not use this variation very often as it seems to be hard on my shoulders.</string>
    <string name="PEC12">Dumbbell Presses\n\nLie faceup on a horizontal bench. with feet flat on the ground lor stability and elbows bent, holding dumbbells with an overhand grip at the chest level: \n • Inhale and extend the arms vertically while rotating the forearms so that the palms face each other. \n • Once the hands face each other, perfom an isometric contraction to focus the etfort on the sternal head of the pectoralis major. \n • Exhale at the end of the movement. \nThis exercise is similar to the bench press. but with its greater range of motion, it stretches the pectoralis muscles. \nAlthough not contracted as intensely. the triceps brachii and anterior deltoid are also used,</string>
    <string name="PEC13">Cable Crossover Flys\n\nTo get yourself into the starting position, place the pulleys on a high position (above your head), select the resistance to be used and hold the pulleys in each hand. \nStep forward in front of an imaginary straight line between both pulleys while pulling your arms together in front of you. Your torso should have a small forward bend from the waist. This will be your starting position. \nWith a slight bend on your elbows in order to prevent stress at the biceps tendon, extend your arms to the side (straight out at both sides) in a wide arc until you feel a stretch on your chest. Breathe in as you perform this portion of the movement. Tip: Keep in mind that throughout the movement, the arms and torso should remain stationary; the movement should only occur at the shoulder joint. \nReturn your arms back to the starting position as you breathe out. Make sure to use the same arc of motion used to lower the weights. \nHold for a second at the starting position and repeat the movement for the prescribed amount of repetitions. \nVariations: You can vary the point in front of you where your arms meet.</string>
    <string name="PEC14">Machine Bench Press\n\nSit down on the Chest Press Machine and select the weight. \nStep on the lever provided by the machine since it will help you to bring the handles forward so that you can grab the handles and fully extend the arms. \nGrab the handles with a palms-down grip and lift your elbows so that your upper arms are parallel to the floor to the sides of your torso. Tip: Your forearms will be pointing forward since you are grabbing the handles. Once you bring the handles forward and extend the arms you will be at the starting position. \nNow bring the handles back towards you as you breathe in. \nPush the handles away from you as you flex your pecs and you breathe out. Hold the contraction for a second before going back to the starting position. \nRepeat for the recommended amount of reps. \nWhen finished step on the lever again and slowly get the handles back to their original place. \nVariations: You can use free weights (barbells and dumbbells) to perform this exercise on a regular bench. Alternatively, you can use the pulley machine as well.</string>
    <string name="PEC15">Push·Ups\n\nLie on the floor face down and place your hands about 36 inches apart while holding your torso up at arms length. \nNext, lower yourself downward until your chest almost touches the floor as you inhale. \nNow breathe out and press your upper body back up to the starting position while squeezing your chest. \nAfter a brief pause at the top contracted position, you can begin to lower yourself downward again for as many repetitions as needed. \nVariations: \nIf you are new at this exercise and do not have the strength to perform it, you can either bend your legs at the knees to take off resistance or perform the exercise against the wall instead of the floor. \nFor the most advanced lifters, you can place your feet at a high surface such as a bench in order to increase the resistance and to target the upper chest more.</string>
    <string name="PEC2">Incline Presses\n\nLoad the bar with an appropriate weight for your training.  nPut on the bench with your feet resting on the floor, driving through your hips. Your back should be arched, and the shoulder blades retracted.  nTake a medium grip, pronation that covers the rings in the bar. Remove the bar from the frame, holding the weight above your chest with your arms extended. This will be your starting position.  n Lower the bar to the sternum by flexing the elbows. Keep control and do not bounce the bar off your chest. The sides should remain tight and the elbows slightly drawn in.  nAfter touching your torso with the bar, extend the elbows to return the bar to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="PEC3">Decline Presses\n\nLie on a decline bench (between 20 and 40 degrees). with the head angled angled down and feet ﬁxed to prevent sliding and grasp the barbell with an overhand grip shoulder width o \n• Inhale and lower the barbell to the lower pectorals with a controlled movement. \n• Extend the arms and exhale at the end of the movement. \nThis exercise contracts the pectoralis major(mainly its inferior fibers), triceps breachii, and the anterior deltoid. \nThis excercise is useful for outlining the inferior groove of the pectorals.Using light weights and lowering the bar to the neck streches the pectoralis major correctly.The decline press may be performed at a frame that guides the bar.</string>
    <string name="PEC4">Close-Grip Bench Presses\n\nLie on a horizontal bench with the buttocks on the bench and the teet on the ground, gripping the barbell with an overhand grip and wrists 4 to 15 inches apart, depending on the ﬂexibility of the wrists: Inhale and lower the bar with a controlled movement to the chest, with the elbows out to the side. Extend and exhale at the end of the effort. \nThis exercise develops the pectoral muscles at the sternal notch and the triceps brachii. (With this in mind, it may be included in a program for the arms) By extending and \nkeeping me elbows next to the body, a greater part of the work is pertormed by the anterior deltoid. this movement may be performed at a frame that guides the bar.</string>
    <string name="PEC5">Dumbbell Flys\n\nLie on a narrow bench that won\' t irrteriere with the shoulder movement and hold a dumbbell in each hand with arms extended or slightly bent to relieve stress on the joint: \n• Inhale and open the arms to horizontal, \n• Raise the arms to vertical while exhaling. \n• Perform a small isometric contraction at the end of the movement to emphasize the work on the sternal head of the pecturalis major. \nThis exercise is never performed with heavy weights. This exercise focuses the work an the pectoralis major. It serves as a basic exercise in increase thoracic expansion, which contributes to increased pulmonary capacity. it also develops muscle ﬂexibility.</string>
    <string name="PEC6">Incline Dumbbell Flys\n\nSit on a bench angled between 45 and 60 degrees, dumbbells in hand and arms extended vertically or slightly bent to ease stress when bringing the arms together: \n • Inhale and extend the arms to horizontal. \n • Raise the arms to vertical while exhalinq. \nThis movement should not be performed with heavy weights. lt focuses the effort mainly on the clavicular head of the pectoralis major.Along with the pullover. lt is a fundamental exercise for developing thoracic expansion.</string>
    <string name="PEC7">Parallel Bar Dips\n\nFor this exercise you will need access to parallel bars. To get yourself into the starting position, hold your body at arms length (arms locked) above the bars. \nWhile breathing in, lower yourself slowly with your torso leaning forward around 30 degrees or so and your elbows flared out slightly until you feel a slight stretch in the chest. O\nnce you feel the stretch, use your chest to bring your body back to the starting position as you breathe out. Tip: Remember to squeeze the chest at the top of the movement for a second. \nRepeat the movement for the prescribed amount of repetitions. \nVariations: \nIf you are new at this exercise and do not have the strength to perform it, use a dip assist machine if available. These machines use weight to help you push your bodyweight. \nOtherwise, a spotter holding your legs can help. \nMore advanced lifters can add weight to the exercise by using a weight belt that allows the addition of weighted plates.</string>
    <string name="PEC8">Dumbbell Pullovers\n\nPlace a dumbbell standing up on a flat bench. \nEnsuring that the dumbbell stays securely placed at the top of the bench, lie perpendicular to the bench (torso across it as in forming a cross) with only your shoulders lying on the surface. Hips should be below the bench and legs bent with feet firmly on the floor. The head will be off the bench as well. \nGrasp the dumbbell with both hands and hold it straight over your chest with a bend in your arms. Both palms should be pressing against the underside one of the sides of the dumbbell. This will be your starting position. Caution: Always ensure that the dumbbell used for this exercise is secure. Using a dumbbell with loose plates can result in the dumbbell falling apart and falling on your face. \nWhile keeping your arms locked in the bent arm position, lower the weight slowly in an arc behind your head while breathing in until you feel a stretch on the chest. \nAt that point, bring the dumbbell back to the starting position using the arc through which the weight was lowered and exhale as you perform this movement. \nHold the weight on the initial position for a second and repeat the motion for the prescribed number of repetitions. \nCaution: If you are new to this movement, have a spotter hand you the weight instead. If not, please ensure that the dumbbell does not fall on you as you arrange your torso to perform the exercise on the bench. \nAlso, as I already mentioned, ensure that the dumbbell used is in perfect working condition. Old dumbbells in need of welding should never be used to perform this exercise. \nVariations: \nYou can perform this exercise using a barbell or an e-z bar instead of dumbbells. \nAlso, if using dumbbells like Powerblocksâ„¢, just use a dumbbell on each hand with the palms of your hands facing each other.</string>
    <string name="PEC9">Barbell Pullovers\n\nLie on a flat bench with a barbell using a shoulder grip width. \nHold the bar straight over your chest with a bend in your arms. This will be your starting position. \nWhile keeping your arms in the bent arm position, lower the weight slowly in an arc behind your head while breathing in until you feel a stretch on the chest. \nAt that point, bring the barbell back to the starting position using the arc through which the weight was lowered and exhale as you perform this movement. \nHold the weight on the initial position for a second and repeat the motion for the prescribed number of repetitions. \nVariations: \nYou can perform this exercise using a dumbbell or an E-Z bar instead of dumbbells.</string>

    <!-- Back data -->
    <string name="ESP1">Lat Pull-Downs\n\nSit facing the machine with the legs positioned under the pads, gripping the bar in with a wide overhand grip: Inhale and pull the bar down to the sternal notch while putting out the chest and pulling the elbows back. Exhale at the end of the movement. \nThis exercise develops the bulk of the back. It mainly works the upper and central fibers at the latissimus dorsi. The middle and lower portions of the trapezius. the rhomboids, the biceps brachii, the brachialis, and, to a lesser extent, the pectorals also contract.</string>
    <string name="ESP10">Chin-Ups\n\nGrab the pull-up bar with the palms facing your torso and a grip closer than the shoulder width. \nAs you have both arms extended in front of you holding the bar at the chosen grip width, keep your torso as straight as possible while creating a curvature on your lower back and sticking your chest out. This is your starting position. Tip: Keeping the torso as straight as possible maximizes biceps stimulation while minimizing back involvement. \nAs you breathe out, pull your torso up until your head is around the level of the pull-up bar. Concentrate on using the biceps muscles in order to perform the movement. Keep the elbows close to your body. Tip: The upper torso should remain stationary as it moves through space and only the arms should move. The forearms should do no other work other than hold the bar. \nAfter a second of squeezing the biceps in the contracted position, slowly lower your torso back to the starting position; when your arms are fully extended. Breathe in as you perform this portion of the movement. \nRepeat this motion for the prescribed amount of repetitions. \nVariations: \nIf you are new at this exercise and do not have the strength to perform it, use a pull-up assist machine if available. These machines use weight to help you push your bodyweight. \nOtherwise, a spotter holding your legs can help. \nOn the other hand, more advanced lifters can add weight to the exercise by using a weight belt that allows the addition of weighted plates.</string>
    <string name="ESP11">Reverse Chin-Ups\n\nHang from a bar with an underhand grip, hands shoulder-width apart: \n • Inhale and push out the chest as you raise the chin to lhe bar. \n • Exhale at the end of the movement. \nThis movemenl develops me lalissimus dorsi and teres major and is associated with the intense work of the biceps brachii and brachialis. \nTherefore, it could included in an arm workout program. \nThis exercise also contracts lhe middle and lower portions of the trapezius, the rhomboids, and the pectorals. \nPerlarming this exercise takes a certain amount of strength; use a high pulley lo make it easier.</string>
    <string name="ESP12">Straight-Arm Lat Pull-Downs\n\nStand and face the machine with feet slightly apart; grip the bar with an overhand grip, arms extended and shoulder-width apart; ﬁx the back and contract the abdominal core: \n • Inhale and bring the bar to the thighs, keeping the arms extended (elbows can be slightly bent). \n • Exhale at the end of the movement. \nThis exercise, which works the dorsi, strengthens the teres major and the long head of the triceps, which stabilizes the arm-trunk hinge.</string>
    <string name="ESP13">Deadlifts\n\nStep 1: Stand in front of a barbell placed on the floor and grasp the barbell with an overhand grip. \nStep 2: Keep head up, lower back tucked in, and do not bend knees. \nStep 3: Stand straight up using power from legs, back, and arms. \nStep 4: Squeeze shoulder blades together at the top of the movement. \nEl peso muerto de la pierna recta es un ejercicio de pesas que se dirige principalmente a los tendones de la corva y en menor medida también apunta a los antebrazos, espalda baja, glúteos, y flexores de la cadera. \nThe only straight-leg deadlift equipment that you really need is the following: barbell and weight plates. There are however many different straight-leg deadlift variations that you can try out that may require different types of straight-leg deadlift equipment or maye even require no equipment at all.</string>
    <string name="ESP14">Meadows Row\n\nStep 1: Load up a bar (or landmine) and stand in a staggered stance with the leading foot perpendicular with the bar. \nStep 2: Next, with the right foot as the leading foot, bend over at the waist and grasp the end of the bar in your left hand with an overhand grip. \nStep 3: Rest your right elbow on your thigh for support and begin exercise by rowing the weight up so that your left hand ends up just outside your chest (just as you would for a pronated one-arm dumbbell row). \nStep 4: Lower the weight back down to complete one rep.</string>
    <string name="ESP2">Back Lat Pull-Downs\n\nSit down on a pull-down machine with a wide bar attached to the top pulley. Make sure that you adjust the knee pad of the machine to fit your height. These pads will prevent your body from being raised by the resistance attached to the bar. \nGrab the bar with the palms facing forward using the prescribed grip. Note on grips: For a wide grip, your hands need to be spaced out at a distance wider than your shoulder width. For a medium grip, your hands need to be spaced out at a distance equal to your shoulder width and for a close grip at a distance smaller than your shoulder width. \nAs you have both arms extended in front of you holding the bar at the chosen grip width, bring your torso and head forward. Think of an imaginary line from the center of the bar down to the back of your neck. This is your starting position. \nAs you breathe out, bring the bar down until it touches the back of your neck by drawing the shoulders and the upper arms down and back. Tip: Concentrate on squeezing the back muscles once you reach the full contracted position. The upper torso should remain stationary and only the arms should move. The forearms should do no other work except for holding the bar; therefore do not try to pull down the bar using the forearms. \nAfter a second on the contracted position squeezing your shoulder blades together, slowly raise the bar back to the starting position when your arms are fully extended and the lats are fully stretched. Inhale during this portion of the movement. \nRepeat this motion for the prescribed amount of repetitions. \nCaution: Performing this exercise can be hard on the rotator cuffs and if not properly executed can cause an injury to occur. Also, if you already have rotator cuff issues, I advise you to stick to the front pull-down version. \nVariations: You can also performing this exercise by bring the bar down and touching your chest. This variation is safer and not as hard on the rotator cuffs.</string>
    <string name="ESP3">Close-Grip Lat Pull-Downs\n\nSit and face the machine with knees positioned under the pads. \n • Inhale and bring the handle to the sternum while expanding the chest and leaning slightly hack with lhe torso. \n • Exhale at the end of the movement. \nThis excercise develops the latissimus dorsi and teres major, \nWhen the shoulder blades come together. the trapezius and the posterior deltoid contact. \nAs with every pulling exercise, the biceps brachii and brachialis contract, and when the palms face each other. the brachioradialis comes into play.</string>
    <string name="ESP4">One-Arm Dumbbell Rows\n\nGrasp a barbell with the palm facing in; use the opposite hand and knee on the bench \nto support the back: \n • Inhale and lift the upper arm and elbow as high as possible next to the body with the \nelbow bent. \n • Exhale at the and of the movement. \nTo maximize the contraction. rotate the torso slightly toward the working side at the end of the row. \nThis exercise mainly works the Iatissimus dorsi, teres major and posterior deltoid, and, \nat the end ul the contraction. the trapezius and rhomboids. The forearm ﬂexors (biceps \nbrachii. brachialis, and brachioradialis) are also used,</string>
    <string name="ESP5">Seated Rows\n\nFor this exercise you will need access to a low pulley row machine with a V-bar. Note: The V-bar will enable you to have a neutral grip where the palms of your hands face each other. To get into the starting position, first sit down on the machine and place your feet on the front platform or crossbar provided making sure that your knees are slightly bent and not locked. \nLean over as you keep the natural alignment of your back and grab the V-bar handles. \nWith your arms extended pull back until your torso is at a 90-degree angle from your legs. Your back should be slightly arched and your chest should be sticking out. You should be feeling a nice stretch on your lats as you hold the bar in front of you. This is the starting position of the exercise. \nKeeping the torso stationary, pull the handles back towards your torso while keeping the arms close to it until you touch the abdominals. Breathe out as you perform that movement. At that point you should be squeezing your back muscles hard. Hold that contraction for a second and slowly go back to the original position while breathing in. \nRepeat for the recommended amount of repetitions.</string>
    <string name="ESP6">Machine Row\n\nStep 1: Adjust the seat and chest pad to the desired position and then sit down. \nStep 2: Place your feet firmly against the foot holders and your chest firmly against the pad. \nStep 3: Grab the handles with both palms either facing in or facing down and let your shoulders shrug forward. \nStep 4: Now pull the handles into you and try to squeeze your shoulder blades together in the back. \nStep 5: Let your arms back out. This completes one repetition. \nEl equipo fila máquina sólo sentado que lo que realmente necesita es la siguiente: sentada máquina de la fila. Sin embargo, hay muchas variaciones diferentes de fila sentados máquina que puede probar que pueden requerir diferentes tipos de equipo fila máquina sentado o maye incluso requerir ningún equipo en absoluto.</string>
    <string name="ESP7">Bent Rows\n\nHolding a barbell with a pronated grip (palms facing down), bend your knees slightly and bring your torso forward, by bending at the waist, while keeping the back straight until it is almost parallel to the floor. Tip: Make sure that you keep the head up. The barbell should hang directly in front of you as your arms hang perpendicular to the floor and your torso. This is your starting position. \nNow, while keeping the torso stationary, breathe out and lift the barbell to you. Keep the elbows close to the body and only use the forearms to hold the weight. At the top contracted position, squeeze the back muscles and hold for a brief pause. \nThen inhale and slowly lower the barbell back to the starting position. \nRepeat for the recommended amount of repetitions.</string>
    <string name="ESP8">T-Bar Rows With Abdominal Suppor\n\n• Inhale and bring the bar to the chest with an overhand grip. \n • Exhale at the end of the movement. \nThis exercise is similar to bent rows and allows you to concentrate on working your back because you do not \nhave to focus too much effort on positioning. \nIt mainly uses the Iatissimus dorsi, teres major. posterior deltoid, arm ﬂexors, trapezius. and rhomboids. \nSome rnachines are equipped with an abdominal support, which eliminates the work of the abdominal and spinal \nmuscles,However, when using heavy weights, the rib cage is compressed ahgainst the abdominal-support pad, which interferes with breathing and makes the excercise painful to perform.</string>
    <string name="ESP9">Upright Row\n\nStep 1: Grasp an EZ-bar with an overhand grip. Hands should be place on the first grip position so that they are only a few inches apart. \nStep 2: While keeping the bar close to your body, raise the bar straight up until it almost touches your chin and your elbows are flared out to the sides. \nStep 3: Slowly lower the weight back down the starting position. \nStep 4: This completes one rep.</string>

    <!--Shoulder-->
    <string name="HOM1">Back Presses\n\nSit with the back straight, holding the bar across the back of the neck with an overhand grip: • Inhale and extend the bar straight up, keeping the low hack as straight as possible. \n • Exhale at the end of the effort. \nThis exercise uses the deltoid, mainly the middle and posterior fibers, as well as the trapezius, triceps brachii,and \nserratus anterior. Although not worked as intensely, the rhomboids, infraspinatus, teres minor, and, deeper in, the \nsupraspinatus also contract. You can also perform this exercise while standing at a frame that guides the barbell. \nVarious specific machines can help with the performance of this exercise.</string>
    <string name="HOM2">Seated Front Presses\n\nSit with the back straiqht and hold the bar with an overhand grip. resting It across the upper chest: \n• Inhale and extend the bar vertically. \n• Exhale at the and of the movement. \nThis fundamental exercise mainly uses the anterior and lateral deltoids. clavicular head of the pectoralis major. triceps brachii. serratus anterior, trapezius and,deeper in, the supraspinatus.</string>
    <string name="HOM3">Seated Dumbbell Presses\n\nSit on a bench. keeping the back straight, and hold dumbbells at shoulder level with an overhand grip (thumbs pointing Inward): \n• Inhale and extend the arms vertically. \n • Exhale at the end of the movement. \nThis exercise contracts the deltoid, mainly the middle deItoid, as well as trapezus, serratus anterior, and triceps brachii. \nThis movement may also be performed standing or alternating the arms. A backrest helps prevent an excessive arch in the back.</string>
    <string name="HOM4">Front Dumbbell Presses\n\nSit on a bench, keeping the back straight. With elbows bent and pointing forward, hold the dumb-hells at shoulder level with an underhand grip (thumbs pointing away from each other): \n • Inhale and extend the arms vertically while rotating 180 degrees at the wrists, bringing them into an overhand grip (thumbs pointing toward each other).\n• Exhale at the end or the movement. \nThis exercise solicits the deltoid, mainly the anterior deltoid, as well as the clavicular head ol the pectoralis major, triceps brachii, trapezius, and serralus anterior. \nVariations: \nThrs exercise may be perlnrmed seated against a backrest to help prevent an excessive arch in the back, standing, and alternating arms.</string>
    <string name="HOM5">Lateral Dumbbell Raises\n\nStand with a straight back, with legs slightly apart, arms hanging next to the body, holding a barbell in each hand: \n • Raise the arms to horizontal with the elbows slightly bent. \n • Return to the initial position \nThis exercise mainly uses the middle deltoid. \nThe three divisions ot the deltoids create a multipennate muscle whose different fiber directions converge on the humerus. Their function is to support relatively heavy weight and to move the arm thruugh its full \nrange of motion with precision. Therefore, it is important to adapt training to the speciﬁcs ot this muscle by varying the initial position of the movement (hands behind, to the side, or in front). This thoroughly works all the fibers of the middle deltoid. Because everyone‘s physical structure is dilterent (length of the clavicle, shape of the acromion, and height of the insertion at the humerus), you must tind the angle of the initial position that is best for you, Lateral raises contract the supraspinatus, although you can\' t see this because it is located deep in the supraspinatus fossa of the scapula (shoulder blade), where it attaches to the lesser tubercle of the humerus. \nRaising the arm above horizontal contracts the upper part of the trapezius: however. many bodybuilders don‘t work above horizontal so that they isolate the lateral deltoid. This exercise should not be pertormed with heavy weights, but instead in sets of 10 to 25 reps, while varying the working angle without much recuperation time until you feel a burn. To increase the intensity, maintain an isometric contraction tor a lew seconds with \nthe arm at horizontal between each repetition.</string>
    <string name="HOM6">Bent-Over Lateral Raises\n\nStand with legs slightly apart and knees slightly bent and lean forward at the waist while Keeping the beck straight. With arms hanging down, grasp the dumbbells with the elbows slightty bent: \n • Inhale and raise the arms to horizontal. \n• Exhale at the end of the effort. \nThis exercise works the shoulder group, accentinq the work of the posterior deitol. Squeeze the shoulder blades together at the end of the movement to contract the middle and lower portions of the trapezius. rhomboids, teres minor. and intraspinatus. \nVariation: The excercise may be performed facedown on an incline bench.</string>
    <string name="HOM7">Alternate Front Arm Raises\n\nStand with legs slightly apart and knees slighly bent and lean forward at the waist while keeping the back straight. With arms hanging down, grasp the dumbbells wlth the elbows slightly bent: \n• Inhale and raise the arms to horizontal. \n• Exhale at the end of the effort. \nThis exercise works the shoulder group, accenting the work of the posterior deitoid. Squeeze the shoulder blades together at the end of the movement to contract the middle and lower portionof the movement to contract the middle and lower portions of the trapezius, rhomboids, teres minor, and infraspinatus. \nVariation: the excercise may be performed facedown on an inclinebench.</string>
    <string name="HOM8">Low·Pulley Front Raises\n\nStand with the feet slightly apart, arms next to the body. Grasp the handle with an overhand grip with one hand: \n • Inhale and rais the arm up to eye level. \n • Exhale at the end of the movement. This exercise contracts the deltoid(mainly the anterior deltoid) as well as the clavicular head of the pectoralis major andto a lesser degree,the short head of the biceps brachii.</string>
    <string name="HOM9">Barbell Front Raises\n\nStand with the legs slightly apart and the back straight, contracting the abdominal muscles. Hold the Barbell with an overhand grip as it rest against the thighs: \n • Inhale and raise the barbell with extended arms to eye level. \n• Exhale at the end of the movement. \nThis exercise contracts the anterior deltoid, the clavicular head of the pectoralis major, the infraspinatus, and, to a lesser degree. the trapezius, serratus anterior, and short head of biceps. \nIf you continue raising the arms, the posterior deltoid contracts, reinforcing the work of the other muscles and allowing you to raise the arms to vertical. \nThe exercise may also be performed with your back to a low pulley and the cable passing between the legs.</string>
    <string name="HOM10">Upright Rows\n\nStand whit wiih the legs slighltly apart and back straight.Grasp the barbell wilh an overhand grip slightly wider than shoukler width as it rests against the thighs: \n• Inhale and pull the barbeﬂ up along the body to the chin keeping the elbows as high as possible. \n• Lower the bar in a controlled manner whitout abrupt movements \n• Exhale at the end os the effort, \nThis excercises mainly usesthe detoid, trapezius, and to a lesser degree, the muscles of the forearms, the gluteal muscles, the lumbosacralis group, and the abdominal muscles. \nthis is a fundamental excercise that is comprehensive and helps develop a Hercules physique.</string>
    <string name="HOM11">Pec Deck Rear-Delt Laterals\n\nSit facing the machine, with the torso against the back pad, arms forward, gripping the handles: \n• Inhale and separate the arms. squeezing the shoulder blades together at the end of the moment. \n • Exhale \nThis excercise mainly engages the posterior deltoid, infraspinatus, and teres minor and. at the end of the movement, when the shoulder blades squeeze together, the trapezius and rhomboids.</string>
    <string name="HOM12">Side-Lying Lateral Raises\n\nLie on one side on the floor or on a bench holding a dumbbell with an overhand grip: \n• Inhale and raise the arm to vertical. \n• Exhale at the end of the mevement. \nUnlike standing raises, which progressively work the muscle to maximum intensity at the end of the movement ( when the arm reaches horizontal), this excescise works the deltoid differently by focusing the effort at the beginning of the raise. Sets of 10 to 12 repetitions work best.</string>

    <!--Biceps-->
    <string name="BIC1">Preacher Curls - Machine Curls\n\n Sit or stand with the arms resting on the support pad and grasp the bar wiih an underhand grip:\n • Inhale and raise the forearms by bending the elbows, Exhale at the end of the effort.\nThis is one of the best exercises for isolating the biceps.\n\nSit at the machine and grasp the bar with an underhand grip, arms extended, and resting on the support:\n • Inhale and raise the forearms.\n • Exhale at the end of the momet.\nThis is one of the best exercises for working the biceps brachii. Fixing the arms against the support makes it impossible to cheat.\nAt the beginning, the muscle tension is intense, so be sure to warm up properly using light weights. To avoid the risk of tendonitis, do not completely extend the arm.\nThis movement also works the brachialis and, to a lesser extent, the brachioradialis and pronator teres.</string>
    <string name="BIC10">Reverse Curls\n\nStep 1: Stand straight with your torso in an upright position. Hold a dumbbell in each hand at arm\' s length, keeping your elbows close to your torso.\nStep 2: Your palms of your hands should be facing toward your torso. This is your starting position for the exercise.\nStep 3: Keeping your upper arm stationary, curl the right dumbbell forward. As your bicep contracts, breathe out. Continue the motion until your bicep is completely contracted and the dumbbell is at shoulder height. Hold this position for a second while squeezing your bicep. Only your forearm should be moving.\nStep 4: Slowly start to move the dumbbells back to your starting position. Breathe in while doing so.\nStep 5: Repeat the movement with your left hand. This completes one repetition.\nStep 6: Repeat the process for the recommended number of repetitions.</string>
    <string name="BIC3">Barbell Curls\n\nStand with the back straight, grasping the barbell with an underhand grip and hands slightly wider than shoulder-width apart:\n• Inhale and raise the barbell by bending the elbows. taking care to stabilize me torso and spine by isometrically contracting the gluteal muscies, abdominal muscles. and spinal muscles.\n • Exhale at the end of the movement.\nThis exercise mainly contracts the biceps brachii, brachlalis, and, to a lesser dugree, the brachioradialis. pronator teres, and the wrist flexor group.\nVARIATION: Vary the width of the grip to work different parts of the muscle more intensely:\n • Placing the hands farther apart isolates the short head of the biceps brachii.\n • Placing the hands closer together isolates the long head of the biceps.</string>
    <string name="BIC4">Dumbbell Alternate Bicep Curl\n\nStand (torso upright) with a dumbbell in each hand held at arms length. The elbows should be close to the torso and the palms of your hand should be facing your thighs.\nWhile holding the upper arm stationary, curl the right weight as you rotate the palm of the hands until they are facing forward. At this point continue contracting the biceps as you breathe out until your biceps is fully contracted and the dumbbells are at shoulder level. Hold the contracted position for a second as you squeeze the biceps. Tip: Only the forearms should move.\nSlowly begin to bring the dumbbell back to the starting position as your breathe in. Tip: Remember to twist the palms back to the starting position (facing your thighs) as you come down.\nRepeat the movement with the left hand. This equals one repetition.\nContinue alternating in this manner for the recommended amount of repetitions.</string>
    <string name="BIC5">Concentration Curls\n\nSit holding a dumbbell with The palm facing forward and the elbow positioned against the inner thing:\n • Inhale and lift the forearm by bending the elbow\n•Exhale at the end of the effort\nThis isolation excercise allows you to control the range of motion, speed, and form of the movement.</string>
    <string name="BIC6">Hammer Curls\n\nStand or siT gripping a dumbbell in each hand with the palms facing each other:\n•Inhale and raise the forearms together or alternately.\n• Exhale at the end of the movement.\nThis is the best exercise for developing the brachioradialis.\nIt also develops the biceps brachii, brachialis, and, to a lesser degree. the exiensor carpi radialis brevis and longus.</string>
    <string name="BIC7">High-Pulley Curls\n\nStand between the pulleys with the arms outstretched in a cross and grasp the handles of the high pulleys with an underhand grip:\n • Inhale and bend the elbows to bring the hands toward the body. Exhale at the end of the movement.\nThis exercise, which is most olten performed as a cool-down at the end of an arm session, focuses the work on the short head of the biceps brachii, which has been stretched and put under tension in the cross start-up position.\nThis exercise also contracts the rnonoarticular brachialis elbow flexor.\nPerform this exercise with light weights so that you can concentrate and feel the contraction at the inside at the biceps brachii,\nSets of high reps provide the best results.</string>
    <string name="BIC8">Low·Pulley Curls\n\nStand facing the machine. grasping me handles with an undehand grip (thumbs facing away from each other):\n • Inhale and bend the elbows to raise the foreams.\n• Exhale at me and oi the movement\nThis exercise focusesthe effort on the biceps brachii and works the muscle lntensely.</string>
    <string name="BIC9">Alternate Incline Dumbbell Curl\n\nStep 1: Sit on an incline bench that is positioned at a 45-degree angle. Hold a dumbbell in each hand.\nStep 2: Hold a dumbbell and perform an incline bicep curl, keeping your wrists as far back as possible. This will neutralize any stress placed on them.\nStep 3: Let your arms hang down to your sides with your elbows in. Turn the palms of your hands forward and point your thumbs away from your body. This is the starting position.\nStep 4: Curl up the dumbbells at the same time until your biceps are fully contracted. Exhale. Hold the contraction for a second when you get to the top.\nStep 5: Move back to the starting position.\nStep 6: Repeat for the number of reps in your set.</string>

    <!--Triceps-->
    <string name="TRI1">Skull Crusher\n\nStep 1:Lie on your back on a flat bench. Your head should be close to the end of the bench. Grasp a an EZ-bar with your palms facing forward. \nStep 2: Extend your arms in front of you and bring the bar back in a semi-circular motion to a position over your head. Your arms should be over your head and parallel to the floor when you complete this step. \nStep 3: Lower the bar by bending at the elbows, inhaling as you do so. Keep lowering the bar until your forearms are perpendicular to the floor. \nStep 4: Bring the bar back up to the starting position, exhaling as you do so. Contract your triceps when you get to the top of the movement. \nStep 5: Repeat for the number of reps in your set. \nComments: Because of Individual variations in shoulder width. valgus angle at the elbows. and wrist ﬂexibility. the hands \ncan be closer or farther apart on the bar and the elbow angle more or less open during the exercise. \nUsing an E-Z bar helps prevent excessive strain at the wrists.</string>
    <string name="TRI2">Dumbbell Skull Crusher\n\nLie on a ﬂat bench and grasp a dumbbell in each hand with the arms vertical: \n • Inhale and lower the forarms by bending the elbow with a controlled movement. \n • Retum to the initiial position. \n • Exhale at the end of the effort. \nThis exercise works all three heads of the triceps brachii equally.</string>
    <string name="TRI3">Cable Tricep Extension\n\nStep 1: Lie down on a flat bench and hold onto the straight bar attachment of a low pulley using a narrow overhand grip. \nStep 2: Keeping your arms extended, bring the bar down over your torso, creating a 90-degree angle. This is the starting position. \nStep 3: Bend at the elbow to lower the bar, while keeping your upper arms stationary and your elbows in. Pull down until the bar makes contact with your forehead. Inhale while you perform this movement. \nStep 4: Flex your triceps as you raise the bar back to its starting position. Exhale while you do so. \nStep 5: Hold for a second in the contracted position and repeat for the number of reps in your set.</string>
    <string name="TRI4">Push-Downs\n\nStand with the back to the machine and grasp the handle with an overhand grip, keeping the elbows tucked into the body: \n • Inhale and extend the forearms, keeping the elbows tucked into the body. \n • Exhale at the end of the movement. \nComment: This exercise isolates the triceps and the anconeus. \nThe variation using a rope rather than a handle engages the lateral head of the triceps more intensely. \nPerforming the movement with an underhand grip requires more contribution trom the medial head of triceps. \nHold an isometric contraction for one or two seconds at the end of the movement to feel the eflort more intensely. \nWhen using heavy weights, lean forward with the torso. Beginners can use this exercise to develop enough strength \nto move on to more difficult exercises.</string>
    <string name="TRI5">Reverse Push-Downs\n\nStep 1: Feet shoulder width apart, face a high pulley machine with an attached bar at shoulder level height and grasp it with your palms facing up (supinated). \nStep 2: Keeping your body stationary, exhale as you lower the bar by completely extending your arms downward into the starting position. \nStep 3: Keeping your body stationary, inhale as you slowly return the bar to shoulder level. \nStep 4: Exhaling, return to the starting position. \nStep 5: Repeat for a complete set.</string>
    <string name="TRI6">One-Arm Reverse Push-Downs\n\nWith your right hand, grasp a single handle attached to the high-cable pulley using a supinated (underhand; palms facing up) grip. You should be standing directly in front of the weight stack. \nNow pull the handle down so that your upper arm and elbow are locked in to the side of your body. Your upper arm and forearm should form an acute angle (less than 90-degrees). You can keep the other arm by the waist and you can have one leg in front of you and the other one back for better balance. This will be your starting position. \nAs you contract the triceps, move the single handle attachment down to your side until your arm is straight. Breathe out as you perform this movement. Tip: Only the forearms should move. Your upper arms should remain stationary at all times. \nSqueeze the triceps and hold for a second in this contracted position. \nSlowly return the handle to the starting position. \nRepeat for the recommended amount of repetitions and then perform the same movement with the other arm. \nVariations: You can use exercise bands to perform this exercise.</string>
    <string name="TRI7">One-Arm Dumbbell Triceps Extensions\n\nSit or stand grip a dumbbell in one hand with the arm vertical: \n • Inhale and bend the elbow to lower the dumbbell behind the head to the neck. \n • Return to the initial position: \n • Exhale at the end of the movement. \nThe vertical position of the arm stretches the long head of the triceps brachii, emphasizing its contraction while working. \nComment: Contract the abdominal core to prevent arching the low back. If possible use a bench with support for the \nlow back.</string>
    <string name="TRI8">Seated Dumbbell Triceps Extension\n\nSit and grasp a dumbbell, holding it behind the neck: \n • Inhale, and extend the forearm. \n • Exhale at the end of the movement. \nThe vertical position of the arm strongly stretches the tong head of the triceps brachii. emphasizing its contraction while working. \nContract the abdominal core to prevent arching the low back. It possible use a bench with support for the low back.</string>
    <string name="TRI9">Seated E-Z Bar Triceps Extensions\n\nSit or stand and grasp an E-Z bar with an overhand grip and arms vertical: \n • Inhale and bend the elbows to lower the bar behind the head. \n • Retum to the initial position. \n • Exhale at the end ot the extension. \nThe vertical position of the arms strongly stretches the long head of the triceps brachii, emphasizing its contraction while working. \nAn overhand grip isolates the lateral head of the triceps brachii \nContract the abdominal muscles and avoid arching the low back. lt possible use a bench with support for the low back.</string>
    <string name="TRI10">Triceps Kickbacks\n\nStand with the knees sliqhtly bent and lean forwerd at the waist,. maintaining a straight hack. \nBend the elbow and hold the upper arm horizontally alongside me body: \n• Inhale and extend the forearm. \n• Ehale at the end of the movement. \nThis is an excellent excercise for pumping the triceps group. \nPerform this excercise until you feel a burn for best results.</string>

    <!--Leg-->
    <string name="PIE1">Squat\n\nThis exercise is best performed inside a squat rack for safety purposes. To begin, first set the bar on a rack just above shoulder level. Once the correct height is chosen and the bar is loaded, step under the bar and place the back of your shoulders (slightly below the neck) across it. \nHold on to the bar using both arms at each side and lift it off the rack by first pushing with your legs and at the same time straightening your torso. \nStep away from the rack and position your legs using a shoulder-width medium stance with the toes slightly pointed out. Keep your head up at all times and maintain a straight back. This will be your starting position. \nBegin to slowly lower the bar by bending the knees and sitting back with your hips as you maintain a straight posture with the head up. Continue down until your hamstrings are on your calves. Inhale as you perform this portion of the movement. \nBegin to raise the bar as you exhale by pushing the floor with the heel or middle of your foot as you straighten the legs and extend the hips to go back to the starting position. \nRepeat for the recommended amount of repetitions. \nThis type of squat allows a greater range of motion, and allows the trunk to maintain a more vertical position than other types of squats, due to foot position and the higher bar position.</string>
    <string name="PIE2">Angled Leg Presses\n\nPosition the back properly against the backrest on a machine, with the feet slightly apart: \n • Inhale and release the safely bars then bend the knees completely so that the thighs touch or nearly touch the torso. \n • Relum to the initial position. exhaling at the end of the movement. \nPlacing the feet low against the foot plate isolates the quadriceps; placing the feel higher on the foot plate calls on the \ngluleal muscles and the hamstrings. Placing the feet wider apart focuses effort on the adductors.</string>
    <string name="PIE3">Leg Extensions\n\nStep 1: Sit on a leg extension machine. Position your legs under the pad and grasp the side bars with your hands. This is the starting position. \nStep 2: Extend your legs to the maximum, exhaling as you do so. Pause a second in this contracted position. \nStep 3: Lower the weight back to the original position as you inhale. Make sure your legs don\' t go past the 90-degree angle point. \nStep 4: Repeat for the desired number of reps.</string>
    <string name="PIE4">Front Squat\n\nStep 1: Perform this exercise inside a squat rack for safety reasons. Set the bar on a rack corresponds to your height. Bring your arms up under the bar; keep your arms up under the bar and your upper arm slightly above parallel to the floor. Rest the bar on top of your deltoids and cross your arms. Grasp the bar for control. \nStep 2: Lift the bar off the rack by pushing with your legs and straightening your torso. \nStep 3: Step back from the rack and place your legs shoulder width apart with your toes slightly pointed out. Keep your back straight. This is the starting position for the exercise. \nStep 4: Lower the bar slowly until the angle between your upper legs and calves is slightly less than 90 degrees. Your upper legs should be parallel with the floor. Inhale as you do so. \nStep 5: Raise the bar by pushing the middle of your foot against the floor. Straighten your legs and go back to the starting position. Exhale as you do so. \nStep 6: Repeat for the desired number of reps.</string>
    <string name="PIE5">Dumbbell Squats\n\nStand with lhe feet slightly apart, a dumbbell in each hand and the arms relaxed, looking straight ahead: \n• Inhale, slightly arch the back, and bend the knees. \n• When the thighs reach horizontal, extend the legs to return to the initial position. \n• Exhale al lha end of the effort. \nThis exercise mainly works the quadriceps and the gluteal muscles.</string>
    <string name="PIE6">Hack Squats\n\nPlace the back of your torso against the back pad of the machine and hook your shoulders under the shoulder pads provided. \nPosition your legs in the platform using a shoulder width medium stance with the toes slightly pointed out. Tip: Keep your head up at all times and also maintain the back on the pad at all times. \nPlace your arms on the side handles of the machine and disengage the safety bars (which on most designs is done by moving the side handles from a facing front position to a diagonal position). \nNow straighten your legs without locking the knees. This will be your starting position. (Note: For the purposes of this discussion we will use the medium stance described above which targets overall development; however you can choose any of the three stances described in the foot positioning section). \nBegin to slowly lower the unit by bending the knees as you maintain a straight posture with the head up (back on the pad at all times). Continue down until the angle between the upper leg and the calves becomes slightly less than 90-degrees (which is the point in which the upper legs are below parallel to the floor). Inhale as you perform this portion of the movement. Tip: If you performed the exercise correctly, the front of the knees should make an imaginary straight line with the toes that is perpendicular to the front. If your knees are past that imaginary line (if they are past your toes) then you are placing undue stress on the knee and the exercise has been performed incorrectly. \nBegin to raise the unit as you exhale by pushing the floor with mainly with the heel of your foot as you straighten the legs again and go back to the starting position. \nRepeat for the recommended amount of repetitions. \nVariations: All foot variations discussed in the foot positioning section apply.</string>
    <string name="PIE7">Machine Adductldns\n\nStep 1: Sit at an adductor machine with your feet on the footrests and your hands on each handle grip. Your knees will be on the outside of the leg pads. This is your starting position. \nStep 2: Exhale as you push your legs against the thigh pads, bringing your legs together. \nStep 3: Hold for a moment and then inhale as you slowly return to the starting position, separating your legs as far as possible. \nStep 4: Repeat for a complete set. \nThe machine thigh adductor is a exercise machine exercise that primarily targets the groin and to a lesser degree also targets the glutes.</string>
    <string name="PIE8">Cable Adductions\n\nStand on one leg, with the other leg in the ankle cutt and the hand of the supporting leg holding onto the machine: \n• Pull the cable across the support leg. \nThis exercise works the adductur group (pectineus; adductors brevis, longus, and magnus; and gracilis). \nTo develop definition of the inside of the thighs. perform sets of high repetitions.</string>

    <string name="whey_protein">Whey protein or meat protein, which is better ?</string>
    <string name="the_4_supplements">The 4 supplements that you shoudl consume if you have low budget</string>
    <string name="how_to_recognize">How to recognize a good supplement to optimize your profits</string>
    <string name="do_not">Do not start a diet that will endosome day start a lifestyle that lasts forever</string>
    <string name="take_some">Take some time to take care of your diet</string>
    <string name="go_to_market">Go to market and buy fresh product</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up to the method</string>
    <string name="balanced_diet">Balanced diet and exercise, the perfect</string>
    <string name="do_you_like">Do you like to cook? Why not sign up for a cooking course in order to get more out of your food ? In this way, in addition to being able to meet people with the cooking, new technologies, new rich, simple and undoubtedly healthy option.</string>
    <string name="in_a_calm">In a calm and relaxed atmosphere. Being aware of what you are going to eat and spending some time will help you possible compulsive and emotional intake. It will help you improve your ability to control with food.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout1_description">The metabolism is defined as a physical-chemical process that takes place in the body and whose function is to process (to use a simple term) the ingested food to take advantage of its energies and nutrients. Virtually the metabolism is responsible for regulating our daily functions so that their role is essential to maintain a balanced life. The higher the metabolic rate, the greater the energy consumption and nutrient assimilation, and therefore, the greater and better results in all aspects of life: intellectual, physical, emotional, etc. At the same time, talking about metabolism comes with the package talking about fat combustion, and the process that takes advantage of the energies found in food. A person with a better metabolic rate can use higher fat reserves, since it requires more energy to maintain their vital functions, from the most basic (such as thinking or breathing) to the most complex (digest food, repair damaged tissues, etc.) . Hence the reason why talking about metabolism is so important when we start our sporting life, because in summary, an improvement in this will help us obtain more optimal results. 1. Increase muscle volume Increase muscle volume is the first step to take into account when seeking to improve the ratio of metabolic rate. This is where the workouts with loads develop a fundamental role, since it is through the heavy work that the muscles can develop, as part of a defense mechanism to survive in a hostile environment. By having a greater muscle mass the basal metabolism increases and therefore the caloric intake of the body becomes greater, allowing the combustion of fat, even when at rest is much more effective compared to an average person. 2. Improve your diet Someone who trains with a lot of effort but who leads a poor and careless dietary regime, very few chances of success will have, because it is through the nutrients that the body can perform its internal functions in an adequate way to show optimal external results. To give an example we can take the case of an athlete who seeks to eliminate excess body fat. Oddly enough, the most recommended strategy to follow is to eat a diet high in healthy fats and proteins, which will allow the body to enter a state of ketosis where accumulated fat will act as the main source of energy. 3. Train with greater intensity When we talk about burning fats, cardio is considered as the alternative par excellence, being that in fact there are many more effective methods to get rid of the accumulated caloric surplus in the body. In this case, the option that is positioned above all is HIIT, or High Intensity Interval Training, by its acronym in English, with which it is possible to burn more calories in a 15-minute session than in a cardio workout Regular for 40 minutes. But beware, that this premise does not refer to the fact that with HIIT there is a huge caloric consumption in neither time, but this is where the fact that they import more burnt calories throughout the day than those burned during the training. When carrying out a session of HIIT, an effect known as COPD is triggered in the body and it refers to the Pöst-Training Oxygen Consumption (for its acronym in English) and that it is a process that leads the body to have a greater consumption energy by requiring more oxygen during the hours following exercise. In this way, HIIT and consequently, COPD, can be interpreted as the definitive way to burn fat while watching television. Of course, it must be taken into account that HIIT is a very intense training method and therefore, under no circumstances is it recommended to be carried out by people suffering from heart problems, being overweight or having a low physical condition. Conclusions As you can already imagine, having a healthy body costs, and not only economically, but also physically and mentally. When it comes to losing fat there are many factors that must be taken into account to achieve total success progressively and thus not stagnate to throw in the towel when you are already halfway. In spite of how complicated it can be at first, in the long run, you will see that knowing all the secrets (which should not be secret) for effective fat burning, will not represent even the slightest obstacle to achieve your goal</string>
    <string name="tips_layout2_description">We know that in the world of fitness we can come up against a long list of obstacles that in one way or another stand in our way, even after many years of experience. But come on, nobody said that the process of body transformation would be easy. And one of these difficulties, which lurks both beginners and advanced athletes, refers to the moment you have to choose a supplement that helps us optimize our muscle mass gains, especially when it comes to protein that, undoubtedly, is one of the supplements Must have in the repertoire of every amateur and professional bodybuilder. And you do not need to go deep into the subject to understand that protein is one of the main allies when it comes to gaining muscle mass. Increase in the recovery, better performance, reach the adequate nutritional requirements, among others, are the main factors by which the protein powder takes vital importance in the life of any passionate to crush the iron, as some would say. But, why is there so much doubt or controversy regarding protein supplements? From the outset, we know that as the years have passed, the scientific research to find the holy grail of muscle building, have advanced by leaps and bounds. Todays bodybuilders are fortunate to have a database a thousand times larger than pure information, compared to bodybuilders who trained during the era of greats like Arnold Schwarzenegger, to mention some example. Unfortunately, the excess of information, although it is appreciated, can not always be used by everyone to the fullest. There are times when handling so much data can be so stressful and frustrating that it ends up causing confusion and, of course, disinformation. A clear example of this? The excess of supplements that, although they have proved to be effective, do not pose more than a nuisance for many of the bodybuilders when they bump into the counter of the sports store to choose the ideal product and see that they have dozens and dozens of supplements to choose from that just does not seem to make sense. At the end of the day what many end up doing (especially the least prepared) is to buy several supplements of different names but with the same function, assuming a huge expenditure of money and without the possibility of achieving better results, by not having additional external help that really worth it. Whey protein and meat protein are two products that are always in the eye of bodybuilders. Although the first of them has more time in the market, the second is also often well consulted because many believe that coming from a source of protein such as meat, may end up offering more benefits compared to its counterpart. But what is true about all this? Is meat protein actually better than whey protein? or, is it the other way around? Then we will examine both later to be able to draw our own conclusions In conclusion After analyzing each of the points mentioned above, we can arrive at the simple conclusion that beef protein is much better in all aspects, buying them with those of whey protein. The popularity of this last product may be due to the fact that it has become a pioneer in the world of bodybuilding, accompanying throughout its career the bodybuilders of the golden age who undoubtedly achieved important changes without the advantages we have today. day. If you have never consumed beef protein, you still have the opportunity to do so and try the benefits it offers. Yes, perhaps for many it can be tedious because it offers a less pleasant taste compared to its competitor, however, this is a small price that is worth paying when it comes to optimizing muscle mass gains.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout3_description">Whether professionally or amatéur, the consumption of supplements is very common in the world of fitness. And is that for decades, the industry has made us believe that to reach the limit of the body in terms of muscle mass growth is concerned, it is necessary to resort to the consumption of these substances. The fact of including this type of products in the diet is already at the discretion of each and if your case is that of an athlete who is starting with their training and want to consume supplements to improve, go ahead, you can always have many options , even if you have a very tight budget. For that reason we have decided to create this little guide that will help you to know the most important supplements on your way to the final transformation of your body. 1. Creatine It does not matter who you ask, but it is very likely that more than 90% of those who know the subject will tell you that the most important supplement for a good development of muscle mass is creatine. Yes, unlike what many believe, Whey protein does not provide as much benefit in relation to cost if we compare it with creatine, which in addition to its low price, is effective for: • Improve physical performance when training • Speed up the muscle recovery process • Increase bone mineral density • Accelerate glucose consumption (increased metabolism) • Reduce oxidative stress due to free radicals that occur with high intensity workouts • Maximize mental performance Many studies claim that to achieve all these effects of creatine is necessary to consume up to 0.25 grams per kilogram of weight, which in summary refers to a person weighing 70 kilos must consume approximately 17.5 grams of creatine a day. If we take into account that the chicken breast provides only 3.4 grams of creatine per kilogram, reaching the recommended figure is extremely difficult, if not impossible, even if we are willing to consume exuberant amounts of food in our day to day. 2. Protein Whether it is whey protein, soy protein, meat protein, etc., it is a highly recommended type of product for anyone who is starting out in the world of muscle building. Unlike creatine, the protein provides all the amino acids that the body requires to perform all its functions, including giving way to muscle growth. However, the reason why the consumption of creatine over protein is recommended is because the latter does not provide the necessary amounts of amino acids to maximize the expected results. Come on, that the rest of essential amino acids can be obtained through the diet, while the amino acids necessary for the formation of creatine (L-arginine, Glycine and L-Methionine) are not so abundant, but simply sufficient for the average needs . The protein powder can be obtained in any supplement store or sports stores, even in some gyms it is completely normal to see some boats for sale. 3. Fish oil and multivitamins Multivitamins, although not essential, can make the difference between optimal performance and mediocre performance. It is true that most of the vitamins and minerals are obtained through food, however, due to the hectic current pace of life that many of us have today, it is difficult to prepare more elaborate meals with a high variety of fruits and vegetables. They are responsible for providing these nutrients. This is where multivitamins come into play, which are even necessary for many people who, in addition to not training, do not pay much attention to the foods they consume on a daily basis. 4. Pre-training If your budget allows it, you can even give higher priority to pre-workout supplements over multivitamins. This is because, as we mentioned before, vitamins and minerals can be easily obtained through the diet, while the benefits of a pre-workout supplement, we will hardly get them in this way. This is because supplements of this type are aimed at improving performance when performing routine exercises that may be overshadowed by the stress of everyday activities. In other words, a pre-training supplement not only helps to have a better performance, but also gives us that energy necessary to find the motivation that is often affected by the fatigue caused by the tasks of modern life.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout4_description">The world of sports supplements is so vast that literally, today we can find in the market hundreds of dozens of products that promise to optimize our profits, depending on the objective we have in mind. The number of options is so high that for someone who has never consumed any supplement can find tedious the fact of having to choose one without the fear of throwing your money because it does not suit your needs, or has been manufactured by a company that offers products of dubious origin and of which there is no favorable record as to the effectiveness of these. 1: Choose products from recognized brands You must bear in mind that in this case we are talking about supplements, that is, a product that will take you to the body and that will surely play a fundamental role in the way you get your results. Due to the importance of this, take into account the products of the most recognized brands as the first option, even if they are alternatives that have a higher cost, because at the end of the day they have the backing of a company with journey in the world of fitness and that surely more than one person will recommend you without thinking. 2: Beware of new arrivals Due to the large number of options we have available, not everyone risks making large investments in the supplement market, so be very careful with the new brands that appear overnight. Remember that manufacturing or synthesizing a supplement requires a thorough investigation that can last up to years, so as far as possible, try to avoid buying brand new products, unless you are sure that behind them there is a clinical certification or at least it has been scientifically proven to measure the effectiveness of what is offered. 3: It does not only matter who makes them, but also who sells them Remember that between making a supplement from scratch and finally selling it on the market, there is a big difference. Many do not know this and therefore, there are those who take advantage to sell the supplements in sporadic places or even exclusively in online stores to make a business only beneficial for them, leaving the consumer with the tail between the legs. And is that if you find very tempting offers such as discounts of 50 or 60%, but these are only available through the Internet, it is very likely that this is because what they are selling is not really a supplement or , it may be an expired product that must be removed from the inventory. Even, in the worst case, it may happen that what you are buying are actually hormones that work as anabolics, which are illegal substances in most countries. 4: Leave the product the benefit of the doubt Finally, if you see that the product is reliable enough to give it a chance, you can do so by purchasing the smallest or most affordable presentation you can find. Once you have the product in hand, keep training in the same way, feed yourself as usual and consume the supplement as indicated on the label. Do this for a month and take a detailed record of your measurements, sensations after having taken it, those that occur throughout the day and also those that you feel when you train. After having spent this time, if everything goes without a complication, summarize everything you wrote down and compare your results with those of the first day. Did you improve in the trainings? Have you gained muscle mass? Did you lose fat? If you have intolerable side effects during the test, it is best to suspend the use of the product, consult with the doctor to rule out any complications and make way for a new supplement if necessary. In conclusion Remember that while supplements are important for proper development, they are not always necessary. Surely in your gym they will try to sell you from the first days, but before making any investment, first make sure that your macronutrients are possible with the diet exclusively. If not, then go for a supplement, following the above points to choose the option that best suits your needs. Although the supplements are ideal to maximize the results, these will only be effective when the trainings are carried out in the best way and of course, a proper diet is followed, so do not think that just by taking some fitness product you will get remarkable results in a short time, well no; You should not consider it as miracle products."</string>
    <string name="tips_layout5_description">The active ingredient The world of supplementation goes beyond powdered proteins. The market has to offer supplements that act as fat burning enhancers or to solve nutritional imbalances, in order to improve the performance of the athlete, either at the time of training, or during daily activities of the day, as They can be, work. For that reason, it is important as a first point, to know how to choose the active ingredient. An athlete looking to gain muscle, should look for protein-based supplements, while another who is in the definition stage, could opt for an additional fat burner with Egcg or caffeine, which act as stimulants and accelerate metabolism. As already mentioned before, everything depends on the type of objective of each person. Reading the label The label speaks a lot about the supplement that is thought to be acquired, because it contains not only the concentration of the active ingredient, but also other compounds that can be stored in the product. Some labels can even mention the place from which the active ingredient has been extracted, although not referring to the geographical location, but rather to the part of the animal or vegetable. Absorption of the active ingredient While the absorption time of the active ingredient is important to take advantage of the properties it provides, it is very difficult to find the time described on the product label, since most companies omit this small detail in the presentations of the supplements . Manufacturers must submit their products to dissolution tests to ensure that they can be absorbed properly and thus ensure their effectiveness. Allergen compounds It is very important to know if the products to choose have or not with ingredients that can unleash a sensibility in the organism of the one who thinks to consume them. For example, a person who is allergic to dairy products should avoid the consumption of supplements made in machines that use milk for the manufacture of others, or that already include lactose in the product, such as whey protein. Another of the most frequent consternations about supplements is their possible content of gluten, a wheat protein that causes unfavorable reactions in people suffering from celiac disease. In these cases, it is best to opt for products that include the legend hypoallergenic on the label, or those that mention specifically not contain some common allergenic ingredients such as wheat, gluten, lactose, nuts, etc. Lifetime of the products The pieces of cotton that are included in the packaging of some vitamin supplements, or even drugs in the form of capsules or tablets are known as desiccants and their function is to act as a harmless for the absorption of moisture found inside of the container, to allow the pills to remain dry and in good condition for a longer time. However, the desiccant is only effective until the product is opened for the first time, so in doing this, the most recommended is to discard the cotton, since it will not be able to continue to absorb moisture any longer, so that all the accumulation It would fall on the pills, deteriorating its quality.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout6_description">Start a lifestyle that lasts forever. Look for a healthy and balanced diet and lifestyle according to your tastes, your habits, lifestyle and goals. In this way you will ensure that it is a lasting food over time.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout7_description">The pace of life that we currently have makes us not spend much time or pay attention to what we eat. What consequences do we have? Commit health, by consuming more frequently and frequently fast food or unhealthy foods. Sit down to plan your own eating plan. If you know what you have to eat, you will know what you have to buy and it will be easier for you to stick to it.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout8_description">Reserve one hour a week to get closer to the market to buy seasonal products. Put aside the calculation of the total calories you consume. Food not only feeds us but nourishes us. You must think of food as a set of nutrients that will help the body to function properly. So focus on choosing foods of good nutritional quality.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout9_description">I advise you to keep in mind the dish method that will help you ensure that they are balanced, several and to delimit quantities. Always give preference, with half of your plate, to both raw and cooked vegetables. With salads the amount ingested is not usually enough, so you should not forget to also consume vegetables. A quarter of a plate should be protein in the form of egg, meat, fish, seafood, vegetable protein or legume. The other quarter of the plate should be composed of carbohydrates such as pasta, rice, potato or bread. The dessert can be a piece of fruit or a dairy dessert.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout10_description">Mark it on the calendar, introduce it into your daily routine, so that the excuses of our day to day can not do it. The practice of physical exercise on a regular basis will help you improve your fitness and your health. In addition, it generates endorphins and brings well-being. Look for a sport that you like, that makes you enjoy and that you find it easy to introduce in your day to day.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout11_description">Food is still one of the greatest pleasures we have, so you can also enjoy eating healthy. If there are foods that you do not like, nothing happens. Focus on those foods that you can if you can eat, that you like, in this wide range of possibilities you have and not in that large minority that you should limit. Go ahead and try new foods, combinations that allow you not only to eat well, but to enjoy it.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout12_description">Can you take a perfect diet? Is life? Are we? Of course not, so we should not demand to do everything perfect. If so, you will not appreciate the small advances or improvements you make in your areas and the minimum, you will feel frustrated and unmotivated. It is not a perfect diet what you should get, but a healthy and balanced behavior and lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="tips_layout13_description">Clean the pantry. The presence at home of healthy foods increases the chance of success. It could be said that it is a determining factor of short and long-term success. If you have nothing prepared and you have to improvise, having unhealthy foods in your pantry or refrigerator will make it difficult for you to eat well or eat what you had in mind.</string>


    <string name="how_to_accelerate">How to accelerate your metabolism to lose weight fast</string>
<string name="atras">Back</string>
<string name="b">Squats</string>
<string name="ba">Step Ups Jump</string>
<string name="baDesc">Place yourself in front of an exercise box, raise the left leg and then the right until it is full of it, then lower the right leg and equal the left, this will be a repetition</string>
    <string name="guide_to_choose_your_sepplement">Guide to choose your sepplement</string>
    <string name="enjoy_your_food">Enjoy your food</string>
    <string name="in_your">If your are on diet, do not go self-demanding</string>
    <string name="improve_your_enviroment">Improve your enviroment</string>
    <string name="eat_consciously">Eat consciously</string>
    <string name="he_chef">Get the chef you have inside</string>
    <string name="how_to_acclerate">How to accelerate your metabolism to lose weight fast</string>
    <string name="why_protein">Why protein or meat protein, which is better ?</string>
    <string name="get_the_chef">Get the chef you have inside</string>
    <string name="if_you_are">if your are on a diet, do not go self-demanding</string>

>>>>>>> 575f92a86ccb92d34054bc35ba77a7bc399058c8
</resources>
